They can't persecute someone
who's yet to be born.
Right, Garp?
So please look after my child.
Your true father is Gold
Roger, THE King of the Pirates!
So for all these years
gold roger had a son.
This is massive news call the
head office issue an extra.
Then it survived.
His bloodline.
Roger's bloodline lives.
Every time the rain no longer falls.
And I see the sky.
I think back to when I was a child.
Who could only cry.
Blindly chasing after him.
I fall far behind.
My only thought.
One day I will be stronger.
Brattery and gratitude.
Fading with the wind.
Am I stronger now than I was before.
Or as weak as back then.
I don't know for sure.
But until I do.
My voyage will not end.
No matter what's next.
I'm walking straight ahead.
So let's go.
There's nothing that can stop us now.
Though time's all on our side.
We'll never let it pull us down.
And we may fall.
But we'll always keep on standing.
There's no way anything will take
what I hold dear away from me.
The voices inside me.
Push me to keep surviving.
I'll go on.
I'll get through.
No matter what I gotta do.
The fiercest thoughts
of all can pour upon me.
I don't care why in the
world would I turn back.
So let's go.
There's nothing that can stop us now.
Though time's not on our side.
We'll never let it pull us down.
And we may fall.
But we'll always keep on standing.
There's no way anything will take
what I hold dear away from me.
I know the future's there for us to see.
Then Ace isn't Luffy's
real brother after all.
Gold Roger?
He's his son?
Huh a miracle the little bastard
survived this long we know the story the
navy executed every person they could
find who was connected to roger in any
way but i always thought his father
was dragon that's luffy's father right
and their brothers yeah that's what i
thought too what's What's the deal here?
Does Luffy know about this
and he never told anyone?
You're never gonna believe this,
but I've got a baby on the way.
A boy, I bet.
For obvious reasons, I sadly won't
be there for the kid's birth.
Why the hell are you telling
this to a Navy officer?
What are you thinking?
You realize what'll happen?
Are you trying to get the mother
of your own damn child executed?
I'm telling you so that doesn't happen.
There's no doubt the
government will manage
to dig up my whereabouts
for the past year.
And when they do, they'll
find her and get her.
Would you approve of them punishing
a child who hasn't even been born?
You and I have tried to kill each other.
More times than I can count.
That aside.
I know you're an honorable man.
One that I can trust.
Look after my child.
Why me you selfish bastard?
Because...
I know that you'll do it.
Keep him safe for me.
Please, Scrap.
Are you sure this is the
island we're looking for?
It's gotta be there.
Have been a lot of rogers
sightings reported here?
They say he wasn't acting like a
pirate but instead like a man in love.
The navies put rogers
era to an end and we've
got to cut the bloodline
to keep it that way.
Check for pregnancy tests.
If they happened within 10 months of
his capture, I want to know about it.
Round up any pregnant women.
And kill any suspicious
mothers on the spot.
This month, five were born.
There are several due next month.
Not yet.
You have to hold on a while longer.
I'm sorry.
Not yet.
if
it's
a girl, Anne,
and if it's a boy, Ace?
Those names, he picked them.
So his name is Goldie Ace.
Our son, our little boy.
Rouge! Rouge!
Stay with us!
I'm gonna need you to
raise this child, Dadan.
Oh hell no!
Whose baby is this?
What? Why?
I said so.
Starting today, you're with Dadan.
Help!
You're staying with her family,
and that's the end of it.
And be nice to them.
We've both got the blood of
criminals flowing through our veins.
That was the only gift
those bastards ever gave us.
I took the name Portgas from my
mother because I owe her so much.
But I don't owe my father a damned thing.
He can keep his name.
Whitebeard is my only father.
Got it, old man.
Oh, Garp.
Two years ago, you took your
mother's maiden name as your own,
and with your exquisite
speed and strength,
you quickly gained notoriety
throughout the world?
as the underlining captain
of the Spade Pirates.
and that's when we put
the pieces together.
There was no doubt that Roger's
blood had been passed on.
But Whitebeard came to the same
realization and got to you before we did.
In order to secure your mantle
as the next king of the pirates,
he warmly accepted the son of
his own rival aboard his ship.
That's not true!
I joined my father's crew in
order to make him the next king.
Nobody believes that, except you.
Why do you think it took us
so long to finally catch you?
You were under Whitebeard's protection.
So today,
we know that if you were to go free,
you'd use your abilities
to become the next king.
The only recourse we have to avoid
this inevitable risk is to execute you.
Even if it means we face the
prospect of war with Whitebeard.
We
have
a situation,
Fleet Admiral, the gate of justice.
It's opening without
any order from us, sir.
And we can't make contact
with the control room.
What did you say?
Hey, it worked!
Now that's unexpected. It's opening.
Are they actually letting us in?
But that Navy guy said they were going
to leave us on the top curtain to run.
It's not the control room.
That's in Marineford.
So who's behind this then?
Keep opening just a little more now?
Yes.
Keep going.
There we go. There we go.
One little further.
Hey!
Wait, Captain Buggy!
Are you almost there?
You're really opening it!
He's our savior!
He's the chosen one! Okay?
Wait! Oh!
Would you stop milking it?
This is clearly a trick!
Seriously?
Who is opening the gate?
Maybe the universe really does
want me to be king of the pirates.
They're here!
Ready battle stations, now!
They appeared out of nowhere.
But how did they get in here?
It's an entire fleet of pirate ships!
Keep an eye out for Whitebeard.
He must be there.
Bohemia Knight Dome.
Thunderlord Mock.
The DeKalvin Brothers.
Whirl Spider Squad!
It's worse than we expected.
They've got just about every big-time
captain from the new world with them.
We've counted 43 ships in total,
and there's no sign of
Whitebeard or the Commanders.
But every single one of them
is a sworn ally of Whitebeard.
All right, Ace. We're here.
We've got your back, bro.
Listen to those children
panic. It's pathetic.
They actually came?
Should we attack?
Not yet.
Whitebeard's got to be
around here somewhere.
He's planted something big,
so keep your eyes on the sea!
Now this is fun!
I'm ready for some war!
Now come on, Whitebeard, I'm hungry!
It's him.
What is that?
Where is he?
You figure.
It's a surprise attack.
Whitebeard is no fool.
Oh, don't act like you're so smart.
There's a shadow in the middle of the bay.
What's happening?
It's just as I've been.
Why didn't we plan for this?
They got their ships coated
to ambushes from underwater.
It's Whitebeard's ship, the Moby Dick!
Three more Whitebeard Pirate ships!
They've infiltrated the bay.
Oh holy crap!
It's First Division Commander Marco.
I'm counting 14 commanders.
They're all here.
Sengoku.
Been quite some time, Sengoku.
Whitebeard...
We've got plenty to talk about.
Like you not killing my son.
I can't believe we let
them get this close.
Well, we're through the gate.
Now, I'm just worried your dear old
dad is gonna make an appearance.
I'm sure those government
boys would love that.
Dad?
Dragon's not the type to sit
back while his son's killed.
When he's on a tear, things get nasty.
Okay, now, me and Ace, we
don't have the same dad. Huh?
You're right about Dragon
being my dad, but not Ace.
His dad is Gold Roger.
Huh?
Yeah, pretty cool, huh?
It's a real shame we
never got to meet him.
He'd always get mad
when I talked about it.
Huh?
Oh, that's supposed to be a secret.
AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!
Hehehehe.
Sit tight for a second, Ace.
FATHER!!!
What did he do?
Did he crack the air?
It looks like he set off a bomb.
Maybe so, but the water level's too high.
A secret!
He's turning the ocean waters against us!
The other side, too!
I knew Whitebeard was
strong, but not like this.
I'm finally heading out!
Kick some bodies take care yeah
you got it see ya in three years the
next time you and me see each other
i'll be way stronger than you sure!
It's about time we show him how it's done!
That brat I can't believe
he became a pirate!
It's a pirate ship!
I've never seen their flag.
He may be new, but he's not wasting
any time in gaining notoriety.
D, where is he from?
We haven't been able to
figure that out just yet.
But he's clearly got the power of a Logia.
Didn't expect the terror of the Grand
Line to be such a dashing young fellow.
Here they offered him a warlord
position, but he refused.
How long have these boys been at this?
They're practically children.
They're rushing like there's no tomorrow.
You sure you want to do this, Captain?
It's too late to complain now.
I've got to see red-haired shanks.
Spade pirates, huh?
So you're the rookie
everyone's talking about.
Came to say hello.
Wait, it's not what you're thinking.
My little brother used to go on and on
about you saving his life when he was young.
So I'm here to say thank you.
Luffy? Hot damn.
I didn't know he had a brother.
Well come on in I'm glad to meet you Papa
squat and let's talk
this calls for a banquet
Hey big guy I bet you
can put me in touch with
White Beard you might be
right but you'd still lose
that bet maybe i could
introduce you but i won't
captain do you realize
that's Jimbae oh yeah Huh?
The Warlord?
Beating him might bring
us some prestige, then.
I'm my own pirate.
I'm not part of Whitebeard's crew.
But I owe him one, so
let's see what you got!
There!
How long have they been fighting?
Five days?
You're both gonna die!
Knock it off!
Ace, no!
What the hell is that?
I heard one of you boys has made it
your life's mission to see me dead.
You wanna fight?
I'm here to grant your wish.
It's the White Beard Pirates.
One of me is enough for all of you.
Fleece bat!
Captain! Captain Ace!
What are you doing?
Get out of here! Run now!
Captain, no!
What's the matter?
Don't tell me you're getting cold feet.
My crew's not trying to kill you.
That's all me.
You let them go!
Giving me orders, you cocky punk.
I...
I won't lose.
You got some fight left.
Look, I'm not gonna kill
you today, all right?
Don't fight it.
You're too valuable to
die in a place like this.
Run wild with us and
our flag will be yours.
And I will call you my son.
Screw you, you old fart!
I'm a good friend to have. Shut up!
Kind of grumpy when you wake up, huh?
Oh, yeah.
You're probably wondering what
happened, since you passed out, I mean.
Well, your crew proved their
loyalty and came to get you back.
So, of course, we beat
the hell out of them.
But they're not dead.
They're all in the ship, too.
Shouldn't I be in a cell or something?
You don't even have shackles on me.
Shackles?
Nah, we don't need them.
Not on you.
Come on!
You know what time it is!
Yeah, we got people trying
to sleep on this ship!
Guys, he went overboard.
I don't think he can swim.
Hey, someone fish him out.
He's been at it every day.
Kid must be stuffed with guts.
Does that make a hundred?
I lost count.
Tell me, why does everyone
on this ship call him Pops?
You don't get it?
Because he calls us sons.
None of us have any family left.
Hell, the whole world hates us.
So it's nice, right?
I mean, I know it's just a word.
But it still feels nice.
What's the deal?
Are you really gonna keep on doing
this even after he's spared your life?
Because you can't keep this up.
Hate to break it to you, but you're
not strong enough to kill him.
So you can either get off
this ship and start over,
or you can stay here and wear the
mark of Whitebeard on your back.
So, you must be Dome.
Hot damn, Ace did it again!
He got Dome and his crew to
surrender all by himself.
You guys want me to command
the second division?
The post has been open for a
long time, so just take it.
Yeah, nobody's gonna complain.
You're part of the original crew, right?
This doesn't bother you at all?
Nah, not no slightest.
I got no ambition for that sort of thing.
Do it for us, Commander Ace.
Well damn I'm surprised I had no idea.
Though to be honest you don't
take after Old Roger much.
He was your enemy, don't
you want to kick me out?
The look on your face, I thought you
had something important to tell me.
But I couldn't think of
anything more trivial.
I don't care.
I don't know where the hell you came from.
We're all children of the sea.
Whitebeard's sure on a roll.
He just picked up another strong rookie.
I heard this new kid can breathe fire!
Please ace come on just calm down
pop said he's gonna make an exception
with this one he doesn't want you
going after teach let me go i'm
his commander aren't i if i don't
bring teach to justice for this how
can that just spirit ever rest ace
i know how you feel but let it go
i've got a bad feeling about this one?
The man killed his own
Gourmet and ran away.
You've treated him like
your son for decades now.
Then he turns and spits in your face.
He's disgraced my father's good name.
I can't allow that.
I'll take care of this on my own.
Hey hold on.
Come back here ace.
Pops.
Everyone else too.
I ignored your advice and took
off on my own why the hell didn't
you just give up on me every bit
of this is my own damn fault.
No
it
was i who
drove you to this my
son that's a lie you
know the damn truth.
You told me not to go
after him but i wouldn't
listen your captain and i told you to go.
Ace was only following my orders.
Isn't that right Marco? Yep.
I heard it myself Then you left.
Sorry for all the trouble really
Teach broke the rules of our
ship, and you had to seek justice?
Everyone in the world knows what happens
if you mess with one of our crewmates!
If you do, you're going to pay the price.
That means if anyone lays
a finger on you, Ace,
they're going to have to deal with us.
Don't worry, Ace.
We'll get you out of here.
Get ready to make hell your
new home, Navy bastards.
I have to admit, we asked for this.
That had better not be regret, I hear.
This is a real mess.
What the?
That's not right.
Here comes the final payoff.
That harmless sea quake
he threatened us with
earlier was just the prelude
to a massive tsunami?
Quake man is what they call him.
Our forces may be many but that
won't guarantee our victory.
Not against Whitebeard, at least.
Before him, his crew, no one is safe.
He has the power to destroy
the world at his veins.
It's happening.
The Great War.
Let's go!
The invaders 47 pirate ships from
the new world led by whitebeard.
The defenders the two
greatest forces of the
government navy hq and the seven warlords.
No matter who wins no matter who loses
the world will be forever changed?